learningmarkets.com 2009-06-17

# Privacy Policy

Can't find what you want? Search here: 

**Learning Markets, LLC Privacy Policy**

Learning Markets is committed to protecting your privacy. This "Privacy Policy" describes how we collect, store and use information on individuals that use this web site. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy please contact Learning Markets directly at [contact@learningmarkets.com](mailto:contact@learningmarkets.com).

**1\. General description of information we collect**

Learning Markets, LLC collects information about our users in the aggregate so that we can provide a more useful service and more targeted advertising. If you choose to register for our Forums we ask for your name, email address, and other optional personal information. We sometimes conduct surveys on a voluntary basis though you do not have to respond to them. 

**2\. Forums**

When you post information in our Forums such features as your Personal Profile, along with your user name, is visible to the public. Whenever you disclose personal information publicly that information can be collected and used by others. While we do our best to protect your personal information, Learning Markets, LLC cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

**3\. IP addresses, cookies and single pixel GIFs**

We collect IP addresses to help us understand how people use the site so that we can improve the service on an ongoing basis. IP addresses are used to compile general traffic information and we will not attempt to identify individual users through their IP addresses.

We also use Cookies. Cookies contain information that websites transfer to your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. The cookies are also used to save the identity of the user in order to allow automatic login to the Forums of the registered user, but only if this is desired. Although we may assign your browser a cookie, the cookie does not reveal to us any additional or personally identifiable information. 

**4\. What We Disclose**

Learning Markets, LLC will not disclose, rent, lend, or sell any personally identifiable information about individual users, except as described in this Privacy Policy. We do, however, provide aggregate information. We disclose such aggregate information (for example, information showing how many people clicked on a particular advertising banner last month) in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties.

We may disclose your personal information as required by applicable law, or in response to legal process, to protect the rights or property of Learning Markets, LLC or to protect the safety of Learning Markets, LLC, our users, or others. 

**5\. Ad Servers**

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by independent ad servers as well as internal ad servers operated by Learning Markets, LLC. Information about your visits to learningmarkets.com, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name or other personal information), may be used in the ad design process. 

**6\. Commercial communications by electronic mail**

Learning Markets, LLC may send electronic communications to you which we believe may be of interest to you but only if you give us your prior consent. You may revoke your consent at any time by sending an email to [contact@learningmarkets.com](mailto:contact@learningmarkets.com) with “unsubscribe” in the subject line. 

**7\. Children**

Our sites are not directed at children under the age of 13. We operate our sites in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and will not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from anyone under 13.
